(Elon:)so you're probably
a good person.
(Howard:)Oh. I made my wife come down,
too.
(Elon:)You think you might
ever get back out to space?
Is that a job offer? 'Cause
I really want to go to Mars.
(Howard:)Assuming I can
bring my wife.
(Howard:)She hardly takes up any room.
(Howard:)She's basically a carry-on.
(Elon:)Well, we're not quite there yet,
(Elon:)but we're always looking
for engineers.
(Elon:)So let me give you my e-mail.
We can stay in touch.
(Amy:)Thank you.
(Penny:)Oh, look.
(Elon:)Someone hardly touched
their pumpkin pie.
(Elon:)Want to share it with me?
A-a partially eaten piece
of pumpkin pie
(Howard:)from a homeless shelter?
With Elon Musk, you bet I do!
(both chuckling)
(Sheldon:)You know, for a
Thanksgiving buffet
(Amy:)in an aquarium cafeteria,
that was really bad.
(Amy:)You're just upset 'cause
they ran out of Pilgrim hats.
(Sheldon:)They gave one to that baby.
He wasn't even awake.
(Amy:)Well, it wouldn't be a holiday
without you being mad at a baby.